SURELY TOMORROW
DONGWOON DAILY
A MONTH LATER
I didn't know.
Oh, you didn't know?
Look.
It's been over a month
since Seo's divorce article was released.
Why are you bringing this up again?
I know. It was released a month ago…
by Jogyeong Daily's Entertainment Team
across the street.
-Right?
-Yes.
That article wasn't a hit
like it is right now.
Are they trying to scout you
by any chance?
What? Oh, no way.
Then why are their number
of views so explosively high…
Dongwoon Daily's Entertainment Team
Assistant Manager Lee Kyeong-do?
That article has nothing to do with me.
Nothing?
Did you just say that?
HER DIVORCE, WAS THERE ANOTHER REASON?
This cafe here.
It's the one nearby, right? Huh?
This is where you went on
about quitting your job
after I yelled at you once.
Is it?
Even though it's blurred,
it's clearly you.
We all know that it's you.
Right, Lee Kyeong-do?
Wait, don't call me by my name.
We're at work…
Okay, Assistant Manager Lee.
Okay, fine, Assistant Manager Lee.
Gosh, this is so annoying.
Hey! Will you look out there? Huh?
Your juniors are working their asses off
to find an exclusive today, but look...
Their assistant manager son of a…
Their assistant manager idiot is…
He provided articles for other media.
Look at this number of views, will you?
It's not about me.
It's about Seo Ji-woo.
Are you kidding me right now?
I'm sorry.
Did you really not hear from her
about her divorce
when this picture was taken?
-No.
-I'm serious.
I seriously didn't know.
Man, seriously.
If you're not busy,
help me pack, you jerk.
What? Are you traveling?
It's no point. It's no point, you see?
There's no point
in devoting my entire life to work.
No point in buying all my juniors food!
There's no point!
Jeez, what's the point?
What are you doing?
I'm packing because I'm quitting.
Oh, if you have time,
pack my stuff in my cabinet for me.
Why are you putting on a show
all of a sudden?
A show?
You think this situation is a joke?
I'm about to remove my desk
because of you.
You can go to Chicago for training,
and I can go home.
What do you think
of this ridiculous situation?
I'm tearing up, seriously.
Goddamn it, this is pissing me off.
Gosh, they were paid to do this,
but this picture is…
They couldn't capture Ji-woo's beauty.
Come in.
Don't we need to get rid
of the articles on Ji-woo?
What for? What does that
have to do with the company?
Who's that man?
Why?
I mean,
it's a scandal right after
all that trouble to get divorced.
It's not irrelevant to the company.
What does it have to do with the company?
Look. When she got caught in those photos
with kids doing weed at the club…
it left a bad impression on the company.
You know that.
But Ji-woo didn't do weed.
Ji-yeon, do you think
people care about the facts?
Before that…
About Jin-eon.
No, now that they're divorced…
That man, Jin-eon.
I know that report was your doing.
Me?
It must've been hard for you as well,
watching how Ji-woo turned out.
What are you talking about?
Or did I not hear that right?
Anyway, thanks to you,
Ji-woo was able to settle it.
Should I say
it's all thanks to An Da-hye then?
What a pop star.
You're Dongwoon Daily's celeb now.
If I buy you coffee, will you shut up?
Yes.
Hey, turn around. Just do it.
-Why?
-Turn.
Are you getting married?
That asshole, shit…
-Hello.
-Oh, hi.
Hey, be honest with me, Kyeong-do, yeah?
Is Seo Ji-woo following you to Chicago?
Your Chicago training
was all planned, right?
Stop the nonsense. Watch the economy.
I'm just curious
about JARIM Apparel's future.
As an economics journalist.
This asshole…
Hey, then did you plan this out
with Doo-jin?
You got Seo Ji-woo to divorce first,
so when she became single, you--
Just pay me back what you owe, asshole.
Gosh, hey. You kicked me too hard.
Why blame him? Reflect on yourself.
Hit a jackpot or step in dung?
A thin line--
Want me write an article?
"Kim Doo-jin on a date with female idol--"
Kyeong-do!
The coffee's on me. We broke up last week.
-Be good.
-Yes!
Wait, you haven't had lunch yet?
Your brother-in-law wanted
to eat together. So I didn't eat.
If your relationship is that bad,
divorce like me.
It doesn't look good
for both sisters to get divorced.
Neither of us met a good husband, right?
MOM
Yes, Mom.
She never spends a day in peace.
Who's that man in the picture?
Mom, Ji-woo is old enough
not to explain every guy she meets.
It's not a big deal,
so you should go work out.
Don't call Ji-woo. Bye.
I'm not a celebrity.
Why are they taking that kind of picture?
I really don't get it. Do you?
You are a celeb.
People always comment
on the price and brand of what you wear.
You should become an ambassador.
I'd better leave soon. This is so hectic.
What did he say? The man in the picture.
Is his name Lee Kyeong-do?
He's probably complaining
that he stepped on poo.
Why did you meet him?
I just met him for no reason.
About the article and…
Hey, Kyeong-do's information
has all been released.
You can't run away alone.
I bet he's not affected by that.
He said he'd meet me
at one of our funerals.
Then the one who puts the incense in first
wins or loses?
You guys are so brutal even after aging.
He never grows up.
What's the point of going to England, huh?
Now that you're divorced,
let's work out together, go on a trip…
and learn the ropes here.
I'm going so you won't make me work.
Should I say...
I'm just sick of everything?
Go only after assessing the situation.
What did Kyeong-do do wrong?
He might die single because of you.
What's wrong with you?
Just go if you're done.
I'm not done eating yet.
Anyway, isn't this delicious?
Good job.
Who else would say that?
It was Deaconess Lee.
She's the neighborhood trumpet player.
She knows everything.
Once she hears it, she won't let it slide.
She'll tell everyone.
She's just a friend. An old friend.
I was happy for nothing.
What do you mean
you were happy for nothing?
Laundry delivery!
It's 12,000 won.
I'll pay you on my way to work tomorrow.
Must prep dinner.
Oh, sure, sure. Go ahead.
Please come again.
I heard she's the daughter
of a big corporation.
I thought you were marrying
into a rich family.
Mom, why are you so materialistic
when you're a deaconess?
Because I'm materialistic,
I haven't become a senior deaconess yet.
Oh, Lord.
I know you'll take care of yourself,
but don't make me pray for more. I'm busy.
It's not a big deal.
My company published an article about her.
She was upset about it.
Don't worry about it.
Laundry delivery!
Oh, gosh, oh…
Damn it, Seo Ji-woo, shit…
Seo Ji-woo!
Oh, my ankle…
You're going to Chicago for training.
Why do you care?
Even if I go, I can't go like this.
I'll be labeled for the rest of my life.
Work's bad too.
Feels like everyone's whispering about me.
Anyway, it's not nice.
It's only for a little while.
No one cares about you.
It even scratched my mom's social life.
My mom was shocked again.
Anyway, Ji-woo can fly off to England
or whatever, but what about me?
I'm just an ordinary, peaceful citizen.
So what are you going to do?
I've thought about it.
It's not exactly a bad idea, right?
Why should I do that?
Well, just a reunion after a long time?
Consider it something like that.
We all meet up for a cup of tea
and post a commemorative photo.
And it seems
Kyeong-do's in an awkward situation.
You know what's funny?
Why are you saying this to me?
What?
He needs it, so why make you say it?
Because he feels bad?
Probably because he's embarrassed.
Se-yeong, do you know what he said?
"See you at the funeral."
Whether you die or I die.
Sure, he wouldn't have the face to show up
after raising his voice like that.
Anyway, he can never see
what's ahead of him.
-Kyeong-do… Now…
-Oh, hot.
Why did he do that?
Show me the way.
To where?
Where is Kyeong-do, that asshole? At work?
But it's the weekend.
The weekend… Okay.
Who is it?
Oh, what the hell? Oh, gosh.
I thought you should talk to her
in person, Kyeong-do.
Aren't you going to invite me in?
But I have to get going.
-Se-yeong.
-See you.
This isn't right. No way. Se-yeong.
Talk to each other! Work things out!
Bye! See you!
Damn it…
Shit.
SURELY TOMORROW
"EPISODE 2"
How can Se-yeong bring a stranger
to my house without notice…
Don't be ridiculous.
You think I'm being ridiculous?
Don't you think you're too selfish?
What, what do you mean?
You did it first.
Taking a stranger to someone else's house
without notice.
SPRING, 2007
It's a relief
that you had your wallet with you.
Did the taxi cost a lot?
What? Oh, I had a nest egg.
Oh, you should've called me.
Then I would've gone to Seoul.
By taxi? Do you have any nest egg?
I would borrow it from other guys, well.
Where are we?
That's Se-yeong's house.
Am I sleeping here?
-The other guys sleep here too.
-The other guys too?
Yes, you don't need to worry.
But we have to walk up there quietly.
Come in.
-This? Are we going up here?
-Yes, go up.
-Be careful.
-Okay.
Come in.
Do you see the bed?
We have to go to the bed.
It's okay.
Be careful.
Let me send a text.
With mine?
To whom?
My uncle.
Go to bed.
Okay.
Hi, Ji-woo.
Hi, how are you?
How do you think I am?
You guys are hypocrites.
Anyway, don't you all have
your own places?
-Yes.
Then why do you sleep at Se-yeong's house?
That's my question.
Hey, the hangover food is not ready yet.
What about you?
I live with Woo-sik.
Now you're clinging to me too.
Stock up on cup noodles.
Thank you for the food.
You said you'd go home. Why return?
It's love, you jackass.
Being called a jackass
this early in the morning?
Imagine it's a replacement for kimchi.
How can a jackass be kimchi?
What kind of kimchi is that?
Stop it. Jesus!
Wait until it's cooked.
What is wrong with you?
Seriously, gosh. I'm so sick of you.
-Are you not eating?
-Who said I'm not eating! Seriously…
Did you eat?
I had something delicious.
If your mom finds out you slept out,
you're in trouble.
If she's still quiet,
you probably covered it up.
Taking care of you
is harder than driving you around, jeez.
Here, get changed. Don't make it obvious
that you slept outside.
Oh, whatever. Everything pisses me off.
I think I was born at the wrong address.
Hey, don't say that.
Your mother's like that
because she's a cold fish.
But the chairman cherishes you so much.
But what's the point?
He sent me into exile in New York.
Why is that exile?
You were studying abroad.
It felt like exile to me.
Anyway, are you going to keep lying?
It's not like you go to this school.
Does anyone know
that you're JARIM's daughter?
Mr. Kim, if anyone finds out
that I am JARIM's daughter…
then they'll start introducing me
as JARIM's daughter instead of Seo Ji-woo.
I don't want that.
Still, if they're true friends...
If they become your friends,
you should tell them.
If they find out later,
they might take it wrong.
I was going to, but…
I missed my timing.
It's awkward to say it now. What do I do?
I have a top secret.
If it'd help you feel better,
I'll tell you.
I'm not curious at all.
No way. That's not true.
I'm sure you are curious.
Gosh, should I tell you or not?
Oh, what is it?
Next week, the chairman and your mother
are going on a trip.
-Is that it?
-That's it.
But how is that…
But it's not the first time
they're going on a trip.
You always make me
go up and down like this…
A cruise.
Six countries in Europe. Four weeks!
Really?
Really.
-Really?
-Really!
Mr. Kim. Mr. Kim, I love it!
It's okay. Go get changed.
-Mr. Kim, really? Really, really?
-It's okay.
"Waiting for Godot."
How's your practice coming along?
As long as Woo-sik does his job,
we're fine.
You mess up the lines more.
I think you need a manager.
-Not necessarily.
-You do.
How will the manager take care of us?
Buy water and… prepare snacks.
Also buy cigarettes?
You really want a younger girl
to buy your cigarettes?
What if we run out of cigarettes
while practicing hard?
I'll have cartons ready.
Thank you.
From now on, I'll do my best for you
to focus only on the play practice.
But why would you?
So I'm going to provide intensive care
for the next 4 weeks…
and you'll have to provide me
with housing.
Wait, housing? Aren't you going home?
Even our house is not stable.
We have overdue rent.
I'll go to Se-yeong's house.
I don't like that.
Kyeong-do needs to practice too,
but the commute will distract him.
You need to give him housing.
Ji-woo, Kyeong-do has only two lines.
But they're important lines.
They're very important.
They're the essence.
See? She's saying I'm not a hypocrite
for the first time.
That's the key to my house. Copy it.
Yes!
Then the key to your house…
You little… The door's open already, jeez.
Down for a drink?
One shot, two shots…
I love it!
Come along, hurry.
Hey, it's on you!
Is it necessary to live together
for four weeks for that?
What am I supposed to do
with your dad during that time, son?
Imagine I joined the army.
You're experiencing it in advance.
How about joining the army now?
Dad, spit three times.
I can't join the army now.
Spit, spit, spit!
Don't you two fight.
Why is that boy excited, honey?
He said he's going to focus on studying.
Do we have any choice but to trust him?
-You like books?
-Used to read that a lot.
-Comic books. It's your favorite.
-A biography like this…
Oh, that's what you read every morning?
-Hey, I think this is new.
-What?
Wait. Do you want to check it out?
Oh, but there's no reason to go in.
We might as well leave.
What?
-Hey, follow me.
-Vintage…
Well, do you want to come back here later?
Sure.
Oh, aren't your parents coming back soon?
Oh… Right.
These last few weeks
were the fastest time in my life.
They're coming back already.
Be careful of the car.
Didn't you say they went together?
Yes.
What do your parents do?
They sell clothes.
That's why you have a good sense of style.
I don't wear what my dad sells.
They don't look good on me.
Wait. Hey, that will look great on you.
I'll work part-time to get it for you.
It's okay.
I don't like that kind of style.
No?
I'm hungry. Let's get some tteokbokki.
Hey, Ji-woo.
Yes?
Let's skip tteokbokki today.
We had that twice yesterday.
But it's yummy.
Sure, if you like it,
I'll eat it even three times. Let's go.
Let's go.
Waiting for Godot.
Maybe it was made for you.
It sounds like "Waiting for Kyeong-do."
Right.
The two main characters
wait for Godot for fifty years.
"Mr. Godot told me to tell you…
he won't come this evening
but surely tomorrow."
Shit…
Godot never comes, but you will, right?
I'm not going anywhere.
I'll always stay next to you.
I'm saying what if.
If I said I would wait for you,
would you come?
Of course, I would.
You know what?
People say men shouldn't cry…
but I'm not going to hold it in.
Why not?
A line in the play says,
the amount of tears is set.
If someone starts crying,
someone else will stop crying.
So…
If I cry a lot…
you won't be crying.
You're so fucking cool.
Oh, will you stop swearing?
Tell a dog to stop pooping.
Where did you learn that phrase?
From Se-yeong.
Hey, you need to leave that house.
You're becoming more and more weird.
Let's run.
What?
But…
Hey, get up.
Why are you lying on the ground?
Hey, Kyeong-do. Lie down.
Why in the schoolyard…
Jesus.
Isn't it beautiful?
Do you want to sleep with me?
If we sleep here,
your lips will get twisted.
You idiot. I didn't mean that sleep.
I meant sex.
Here…
Here?
There's no one here.
Do you mean it?
It'll be memorable.
You know you're a total maniac, right?
Let's do it, Kyeong-do.
Hey. Get up. Get out of my way. Let's go.
Are you crazy?
Let's do it. Today is the only chance.
Hey. Are you crazy? Why…
Let's do it, Kyeong-do!
-Let's do it, Kyeong-do. Come on.
-Stop.
Hey, get up.
Do it! Just do it!
Gosh, seriously…
Thanks!
Do you still want to wear that shirt?
It's that one, right?
It's a similar one.
So lame.
Eighteen years?
Hey, that should be in museum.
I began wearing it recently.
I couldn't throw it out for your sake.
I'm an F.
The neckline is stretched.
I'm just frugal. Hey.
Do you think saving enough
to lease a house like this is easy?
Just be honest with me.
You wore it stretched
because you missed me.
Hey. Forget it.
Why are you stripping?
Besides, I told you
to release an article on my divorce.
Then this wouldn't have happened.
I knew it since you were arguing
to buy pork cutlet…
Hey, whatever.
Settle it before you go to England.
Why do I have to settle it?
Not sure who took it,
but he wasn't trying to capture me.
He was capturing your chaos.
And I'm the scapegoat.
Sure, let's say that.
Then you should've come and asked me.
Why did you send Se-yeong?
What, were you embarrassed
about that funeral statement?
If you're making ends meet as a reporter,
shouldn't you watch your words?
You think you got something on me?
You seem to enjoy this. Here to fight?
I'm not doing it.
Let me go.
Let's do it…
If you want to, act like you want to.
I'm sorry about the funeral statement.
Happy now?
I'm sorry about how you look right now.
PRESS RELEASE PLAN PROPOSAL
All right. Well, something like that.
What was I going to say?
With the other guys and Se-yeong,
you and I will take a natural picture.
It was an 18-year friendship.
Is that your concept?
-So don't make it look like it was love?
-Exactly.
Then what are these brands?
That is…
It's nothing hard.
While taking a picture,
bring me what Seo Ji-woo's wearing.
Why?
You know Kim Ga-eul, the editor-in-chief?
Of a fashion magazine?
Why?
Will you stop asking why?
Well, Kim Ga-eul called me.
She said the main brand
of this month is Louis.
If Seo Ji-woo wears Louis
from head to toe…
they'll take advantage of it.
Gosh, don't you think that's too much?
Didn't I tell you
that I'm about to resign?
Since we're on it already,
we might as well save you, save me,
save Dongwoon Daily's Entertainment Team,
and save the fashion magazine, yeah?
Let's all survive together!
Oh, why me…
All right. But if you don't have
any purses or shoes from this brand, then…
You think I don't?
I'm jealous.
Worry about yourself.
Oh, wear this.
It's perfect to bring back memories.
Hey, whatever. Don't do it.
Gosh, do you even know
who caused all this?
This will be fun.
Looking forward to seeing the guys.
Proceed with it.
Bye.
Oh, right. Don't you exercise?
You're getting a bit of a belly.
Damn it…
Hey. Forget it.
Why are you stripping?
That's great.
Enjoy.
I'd like some too.
Just be honest with me.
You wore it stretched
because you missed me.
You should've thrown it out, you dickhead…
Damn it…
Yes.
I'm on my way.
Oh, did you leave already?
Well, Father's suddenly scheduled
for a meeting.
He was worried
because of the ruckus in the foundation.
What do you want?
Do you want to eat by ourselves?
Where are you?
I'm here. Had some business nearby,
so I came early.
I'll be there soon. Let's eat together.
Sure.
Bye.
When's Ji-woo leaving?
Honey, you should eat.
What are you thinking about?
I don't plan to get married yet.
What?
What about you?
Are you doing this
because your family forced you?
That's what I want to know.
Seo Ji-yeon, are you okay?
You don't look good.
That doesn't mean I don't like you.
It's just everything's happening
all of a sudden. I guess I'm afraid.
So you're saying…
we're getting married soon, is that right?
What's your ideal type?
My ideal type?
That's new.
Here, eat.
The food tastes good today.
Here…
-Eat.
-Okay.
They want to add your picture
in the article.
Why add my picture?
Hey, just one group photo
isn't enough for the article.
That's not enough for the story,
you know what I mean?
If it's too bothersome to find one,
we can use your photo on your employee ID.
Whatever. Oh, don't do that, seriously.
I'm going to immigrate. Don't do that.
Do you have a kimchi fridge in mind?
Get a new one this year.
Everything looks good.
But they're all too big
and take up too much space…
so I'm hesitating--
What? What brings you home?
Oh, just here to find something.
I'm sure I didn't throw it out.
Here…
Oh, here it is.
WAITING FOR GODOT
Let's put it here, honey.
Put what?
It's not like you're moving back.
Take all your stuff with you.
Mom, if you put the kimchi fridge
in my room…
it'd be too far away for you.
I'm going to remove the wall.
For the house to become brighter.
But we still need a room for him.
So when he gets married,
he'd bring his children. That's love.
When will he get married?
I thought he was marrying her,
but she's just a friend.
Lately, I've been thinking,
every time I give congratulatory money
at a wedding, I consider it a donation.
And I always get sick
when I try to eat as much as I paid.
Dad, I'll get going.
Hey. You started this,
and now you dare run off?
I don't think I can.
Hey, Kyeong-do!
You guys overdid it.
-It's not any different from usual.
-I'm the same.
Jeez, you hypocrites.
-Oh, Ji-woo. Come here.
-Oh, Ji-woo. You look so pretty.
-You got so pretty!
-Hi, guys.
Oh, Ji-woo!
Me too. I knew you'd come.
Hey, it's been ages.
-It's been too long, right?
-Yes.
Everyone's here.
Let's take a quick picture and leave.
Everyone gathered to save Lee Kyeong-do.
Right? We're so loyal.
Are you ready now?
All right. Let's take a picture.
Do you still have that?
Questions waste time.
Stay outside. Come back when we're ready.
Why're you in such a rush?
He's desperate.
"Desperate…" Ji-woo, you haven't changed.
I found this.
Wait, what's this?
I should've seen the Godot play
before I left.
That's what I regret the most.
I regret doing it.
You're lucky that you didn't see it.
Hey, this ass--
Woo-sik, don't.
He totally forgot his lines!
Stop it!
"Ji-woo isn't coming."
"No matter how long I wait,
Ji-woo won't come!"
That's what this idiot said on stage.
And then he kept sobbing.
-So, we, we just closed the curtains.
-Oh, stop it.
-Right, right, right.
-And from that moment, he began crying…
"Woo-sik, Ji-woo is not coming. Ji-woo…"
Stop it, you asshole!
Lee Kyeong-do, is that true?
Did you really do that?
I was young, immature, and vulnerable.
I was innocent and sincere.
Sincere, my ass. Do you know
how much we spent on the ticket refunds?
Why cling to the past?
It was your idea to gather
and bring back the past.
Well, is that Louis?
Why wear Louis when my sister has a brand?
The shoes and the bag will do.
I'm wearing Louis, Kyeong-do.
Jeong-min doesn't look like
he's wearing a luxury brand.
Cha Woo-sik, have you ever tried on
a luxury brand before? Yeah?
Woo-sik himself is a luxury brand.
I am the luxury!
I can't tell.
You shouldn't talk about fashion!
I didn't know
we were having a trot singer today here.
Wait, I can see through…
Look here. Dong-won, are you ready?
Yes.
He's handsome. Didn't take after his dad.
Ignore her
and focus on taking the picture.
-Focus on me, okay?
-Okay.
-Dong-won, is the academy sign in?
-Yes, it's in.
Okay, get ready.
All right.
Count before you take a picture.
One, two, three.
Dad, get closer.
-Let's all change the pose.
-Okay.
-Like the beauty pageant.
-One, two…
This is kind of a pressure.
If Woo-sik posts it on his social media,
is your company publishing it?
Yes.
Anyway, thanks.
I got to meet the guys before I leave.
Thanks for that.
When are you leaving?
Next week.
Eat well when you go to England.
I will.
Eat well, sleep well.
Poop well.
Hey, being too explicit isn't charming.
What? Eating and sleeping are elegant,
but pooping is vulgar?
Fine. Eat well, sleep well, poop well.
Be careful...
when you meet new people,
whoever they are.
As long as I don't meet someone like you.
Right.
It's a joke.
Exactly.
Will things calm down
when the article gets released?
It doesn't matter to me since I'm leaving,
but I'm worried about you.
You got dragged into my mess
and almost had your life messed up again.
Wait.
You're wrong.
You got two things wrong.
I never got dragged into it.
And my life
had never been messed up before.
What a fucking reporter.
She never stops swearing.
Why does he have to be so damn kind?
Woo-sik. I just got home.
There was no traffic.
-Hey, Kyeong-do.
-Yeah?
It was nice to be with Ji-woo again
after a while.
Well, there's nothing bad
or good about it…
Man, stop lying. Hey, your eyes
were so busy peeping on Ji-woo in secret.
Hey, I'm tired.
I have no energy to joke around.
You know what?
Well, you'll be at peace if you admit it.
Oh, right! Woo-sik,
did I leave that Godot brochure there?
No, I just…
Oh, hey. That was taken out of your bag.
By whom?
Which asshole?
WHAT IS YOUR GODOT?
Hey, this ass--
Woo-sik, don't.
He totally forgot his lines!
Stop it!
"Ji-woo isn't coming."
"No matter how long I wait,
Ji-woo won't come!"
Lee Kyeong-do, is that true?
Did you really do that?
I was young, immature, and vulnerable.
I was innocent and sincere.
BOY LEE KYEONG-DO
You got two things wrong.
I never got dragged into it.
And my life
had never been messed up before.
"Only if one could entreat Elder Wolha…"
So he can…
It's over. That's it.
Fine, just keep it.
Now, it's over. The end.
JARIM'S SEO JI-WOO'S UNEXPECTED CHARM
'ACTING CLUB'
"The meeting was reportedly intended
as an opportunity
to express frustration toward a reporter
preparing an article
about Seo Ji-woo's ex-husband."
"Cha explained that he released the photo
out of regret...
over how their long-standing friendship
had been misrepresented."
"Meanwhile, this newly revealed photo
of 20-year-old Seo Ji-woo has gone viral."
THE CHAEBOL FASHION ICON'S
DRESS, BAG, JEWELRY SOLD OUT
HER PRESENCE ALONE IS ICONIC…
HER DRESS TOPS THE SEARCH WORD
Lee Kyeong-do, nice defense.
Yes, can you look into...
Where's Secretary Cha?
She went to a meeting with the PR team.
Did she?
Okay.
Are you in a meeting?
I need to look something up.
Can you get me the contact number
of Reporter Lee Kyeong-do?
Ms. Seo is moving alone.
Yes, Director Kang.
She didn't say anything.
She took the taxi.
Okay, got it.
CALLING…
RO-A'S MOM
The call cannot be connected.
Please leave a message…
Where did she go without the driver?
SOMANG LAUNDROMAT
SURGERY DEPARTMENT ICU
-You must be worried.
-Yes.
Let me check the patient.
Here, here.
-Oh, my gosh.
-What, why?
This place has a nice color.
-Enjoy.
-Oh, yes. Thank you.
Wait, I'll eat on my own.
You never did that before.
But they grilled the meat for us.
I can't even grab it for you?
Oh, this is too much. Seriously.
You should've been nice to me sooner.
Then how am I supposed
to thank Assistant Manager Lee Kyeong-do?
Okay.
Is it good?
Totally.
So? Is Seo Ji-woo going to England
or something?
Oh, whatever. It's over now. The end.
Okay.
My forever rival Seo Ji-woo is out now.
It's up to me now.
Why is Seo Ji-woo Jin Han-kyeong's rival?
Hey, it's been 10 years
since I've been asking you out.
That's why she's my enemy.
You're cutting me off
because you couldn't move on.
"Date me and I'll buy you a car."
"Date me and I'll fund your lease."
"I got the Louis collaboration sneakers.
If you date me, they're yours."
You call that asking me out?
I was asking you out.
Good. I like how you're consistent.
Hold on. I have something to show you.
You sound determined.
Ta-da.
I bought a house in Oksu-dong.
Have you seen anyone
buying a house without a mortgage?
Look. That's me.
You're showing off.
Why do you think I'm showing off?
You should move in with me.
Oh, really?
Oh, don't call your mother already.
Come on.
Why are you so hasty?
Still, I should tell her.
-Here, press it.
-Already…
Did that not work?
Jeez, so cheap. Seriously, so cheap.
-Would you move in if it's Apgujeong?
-So call them.
Put that away. Damn it.
Good job. I know that was hard.
So don't say
you want to go for round two after this.
I'm having ice cream.
Seriously, enough with the ice cream.
Hello?
Yes.
What? Where?
That was fast.
Nice to meet you.
This isn't the first time we've met.
We met when you were working
at a hotel buffet in college.
I see.
Anyway, what brings you here?
I wanted to meet you as soon as possible,
and if I came here,
I thought you'd come as fast as you could.
Is it about the article today?
That too, and I have a favor to ask you.
The article about Ji-woo's ex-husband.
Ji-woo already thanked me for that.
Why did you want to see me?
A picture of you two was taken.
Yes, to explain that--
I took it.
I didn't take it myself. I paid someone.
Anyway, I reported it.
Why?
To tie Ji-woo down.
What?
You heard
Ji-woo's going to England, right?
If she leaves now,
she'll have no standing.
And you're the only person
who can stop her.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Ji-woo needs to return to the company.
Ji-woo will run JARIM Apparel
better than me.
You saw the article today, right?
The two-piece set that Ji-woo wore
sold out immediately.
Ji-woo is better at fashion than I am.
Well then. I had a long day today.
Stop Ji-woo.
Why are you doing this, really?
There's nothing between me and her.
Really?
Were you 28? You and Ji-woo.
Look.
After Ji-woo left
and your father's treatment was over,
you spent a year drunk.
There should be nothing between you two,
but you could still worry about her.
Jeez.
What are you pulling at? Huh?
Seo Ji-woo and Seo Ji-yeon.
What are you two women doing?
Our mom is not a good mom.
Not to mention that my husband is worse.
So what does that have to do with me?
Ji-woo will become penniless.
If she leaves now...
In a year or two years...
Ji-woo…
Ji-woo will be a beggar.
My mom is powerless,
and my husband is not a good man.
I'm the only one who can protect Ji-woo.
But I'm…
I'm losing my memories.
I have Alzheimer's.
Divorce isn't the best option.
It'll take a long time,
and my chances of winning aren't high.
If I become blank before that,
my husband will sell the company.
I can't explain everything,
why Ji-woo's likely to become penniless.
JARIM APPAREL
The only way is for JARIM Apparel
to become Seo Ji-woo's company.
My dad and I
are the first generation of JARIM.
And Ji-woo has more than enough
to become the second generation of JARIM.
Please stop Ji-woo.
Next person in line.
If you don't want to talk about old love,
can you do it for your friendship?
Hello. Can you show me
your ticket and your passport? Okay.
Do you have any luggage?
Yes.
Can you put it up here?
Let's talk.
Are you crazy?
First of all, since you're here,
put it up here. It's heavy.
Let's talk.
I have to get on board.
Take the next one.
This isn't KTX.
Sorry about that.
Hey, put it up here first. No, put…
Can I have my passport back?
Sorry, I'll be right back.
That crazy bastard…
Hey, Lee Kyeong-do. Hey!
What the heck is wrong with him?
This is crazy.
Hey, Lee Kyeong-do. Stop right there. Hey!
Oh, seriously.
Jeez.
Oh, sir! Stop him. That guy.
Catch him. Hurry!
Sir, can we have a moment?
Yes. We know each other.
Mom?
Catch him.
-Wait, wait. I'm not a bad guy.
-Let's talk over there.
Come with us.
Wait.
SURELY TOMORROW
I thought it was a color film.
Black and white makes it look cool.
Say it again to Ji-woo's face.
Our matching items aren't visible.
It's not visible!
Why's this a big deal?
Shouldn't have brought the camera. Shit.
I feel black and white.
Let's grab a drink.
Sure, it's on, black and white Jeong-min.
I developed it too.
Don't you have a sense of shame?
Ji-woo.
You look pretty
because it's black and white.
You want a punch in the face?
Let's go. Come on. Let's go.
Kyeong-do. Kyeong-do?
I turned off the gas valve. I ran out of
underwear, so I took one of yours.
No questions, please.
Is running away your specialty?
Did you get on top of him?
I just pulled a prank
to see what he's like.
Do you really like me?
You never blame me even a little.
That pisses me off even more.
What do you want me to do then?
There should be a thesis about you two.
You guys are weird.
I went when I was 20
and when I was 28. I'm worried.
Is it love?